A Finding Aid to the Lucy R. Lippard Papers, 1930s-2007, bulk 1960s-1990, in the Archives of American Art AAA.lipplucy
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1950s-2006; Series 2; 28.8 Linear feet Boxes 1-28, 51, OVs 54-63
  - Correspondence by Subject, 1950s-1990s; 2.2
    - Murals and Paintings on Doors, 1980-1984 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Murals and Paintings on Doors, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Murals and Paintings on Doors, 1986-1992 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Neighborhood Museums, circa 1969-circa 1970 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - New Zealand Artists, circa 1974 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Nicaragua Visit, circa 1983-circa 1984 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Older Artists, circa 1982-circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Peace Posters, circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Politics, Miscellaneous, circa 1972-circa 1974 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Postcards, Center for Constitutional Rights, circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Public Art, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 20-22)
    - Public Art, 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Public Art, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Public Art, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Public Art, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Public Art, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Public Art, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 28-29)
    - Public Art, circa 1979 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Public Art, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 31-32)
    - Public Art, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
    - Public Art, circa 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Public Art, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 5-8)
    - Public Art, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Public Art, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Public Art, 1984-1988 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Public Art, 1990-1994 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Reproductions of Artwork, circa 1950s-circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 13-18)
    - Reproductive Rights, circa 1979-circa 1984 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Reproductive Rights, circa 1989-circa 1991 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Reproductive Rights, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Reproductive Rights, 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Reproductive Rights, 1985-1991 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Reproductive Rights, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Reproductive Rights, "Wake Up Little Suzie" Exhibition Comments, circa 1992 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Royalties for Artists, circa 1971-circa 1974 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Software Exhibition at the Jewish Museum, circa 1970 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Style (Life) Alienation, 1970s (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Union 1199 and Workers Art, circa 1970s-circa 1990s (Box 27, Folder 29-30)
    - Union 1199 and Workers Art, circa 1970s-circa 1990s; 1 Sound cassettes Label reads "2nd Sunday Oct 9th" (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Union 1199 and Workers Art, circa 1976-1981 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Union 1199 and Workers Art, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Union 1199 and Workers Art, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Union 1199 and Workers Art, 1990-1993 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - U.S. Culture and Events in Central America, circa 1982-circa 1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Culture and Events in Central America, 1982-1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Culture and Events in Central America, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Vietnam War, circa 1968-circa 1973 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Vietnam War, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Women and Nature, circa 1966-1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - World Affairs Conference, circa 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
    - World Affairs Conference, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Oversized Artists Rights/Contracts housed with Box 21, Folder 21 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Central Europe housed with Box 22, Folder 29 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Color Cartoons housed with Box 23, Folder 10 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Mail Art, Send Slips to Lucy Lippard, housed with Box 26, Folder 2 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Media Analysis/Imagery housed with Box 26, Folder 5 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Public Art housed with Box 26, Folder 30 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Reproductions of Artwork housed with Box 27, Folders 13-18 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Alternative Movements/Spaces housed with Box 21, Folder 7 (Box OV 62)
    - Oversized Australia housed with Box 21, Folders 22-23 (Box OV 62)
    - Oversized Mail Art housed with Box 25, Folder 25 (Box OV 62)
    - Oversized Public Art housed with Box 26, Folder 20 and 31-32 (Box OV 62)
    - Oversized Public Art housed with Box 27, Folder 2 (Box OV 62)
    - Oversized U. S. Culture and Events in Central America housed with Box 28, Folder 1 (Box OV 62)
    - Oversized Architectural and Environmental Art housed with Box 21, Folder 12 (Box OV 63)
    - Oversized Censorship housed with Box 21, Folder 35 and Box 22 Folder 7 (Box OV 63)
    - Oversized Central America housed with Box 22, Folder 14 (Box OV 63)
    - Oversized Central America, Printed Material housed with Box 22, Folder 16 (Box OV 63)
    - Oversized Columbus and Art, Quincentennial housed with Box 23, Folder 25-28 (Box OV 63)
    - Oversized Public Art housed with Box 27 Folders 10-11 (Box OV 63)
- Writings, 1930s-1990s; Series 3; 13.24 Linear feet Boxes 28-41, 51-52, OVs 64-66
  The series is arranged as 2 subseries.
  2.1: Writings by Lippard, 1930s-1990s
  2.2: Writings by Others, 1960s-1990s
  Correspondence, manuscript drafts and galleys, extensive notes, publication records, research material including artist-related correspondence and printed matter, and photographs, document Lippard's prolific writings on the subjects of individual artists such as Philip Evergood, Eva Hesse, Ad Reinhardt, and Tony Smith, conceptual, minimalist, post-minimalist and feminist art, and the relationship between art and activism.
  Recordings include 1 sound cassette, 1 sound disc (vinyl), 11 sound tape reels, and 1 electronic disc (CD).
  - Writings by Lippard, 1930s-1990s; 3.1
    Records are arranged by format in which the writings were produced i.e. books, columns, conferences and symposia, interviews, lectures and speeches, and other writings, and are arranged alphabetically by title thereafter.
    The series documents Lippard's writing activities, primarily from the 1960s to the 1990s, and provides insight into the content and process of her writing for books, columns, essays, and lectures.
    Lippard's most renowned writings from this period, including her seminal text on conceptual art, Six Years: The Dematerialization of the Art Object (1973), her mongraph on Eva Hesse (1976), Get the Message?: A Decade Of Art For Social Change (1984), and Mixed Blessings: New Art in a Multicultural America (1990), are represented here. The series also includes Lippard's early "New York Letter" manuscripts written for Art International, and circa 100 additional essays written for publications such as Artforum, Art Voices and Hudson Review, including "The Pink Glass Swan" and "Trojan Horses: Activist Art and Power" (1984), as well as essays written for exhibitions on artists such as Rudy Burckhardt, Sol LeWitt, Ree Morton, and James Rosenquist. Also found are records documenting Lippard's role as co-editor for the Alliance for Cultural Democracy handbook How to '92: Model Actions for a Post-Columbian World.
    Correspondence found in this series primarily relates to contracts and other aspects of the publication process, but there is also some correspondence with, and related to, artists including two folders of correspondence from Philip Evergood written to Lippard as she was writing The Graphic Work of Philip Evergood (1966), a detailed letter from Ethelyn Haig concerning recollections of Eva Hesse, photocopies of Hesse's correspondence and interviews, and some photocopies of correspondence from Ad Reinhardt.
    The series also includes transcripts, notes and related material, including some audio recordings, of 5 interviews of Lippard and 6 interviews conducted by Lippard. These have been arranged as part of this series because they are annotated and edited by Lippard. They include recordings of interviews of Donald Judd and Robert Mangold in 1965 and 1968, transcripts of Lippard's interviews of Sol LeWitt and Tony Smith, and transcripts of interviews of Lippard conducted by Scott Marsden, and Ursula Meyer. Also found is the transcript of an interview regarding Lippard's 1998 book The Lure of the Local.
    From 1970 to 1976 Lippard's speaking engagements at art schools were confined to answering written questions submitted by audiences; this series includes an extensive selection of these "questions addressed to Lippard in art schools." There are files on symposia and conferences which include notes and texts for Lippard's contributions and transcripts and notes of panel discussions edited by Lippard for publication.
    Additional writings for exhibition catalogs can be found in Series 5.
    - Books, Ad Reinhardt (1985) (Box 28)
      - Bibliography, circa 1966-1970 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Chronology, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1982 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Footnotes, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 28, Folder 16-17)
      - Illustrations, circa 1950s-circa 1970s (Box 28, Folder 18-19)
      - Lists of Color Plates and Captions, circa 1970s (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Manuscript, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 28, Folder 21-22)
      - Manuscript, Epilogue, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - Notes, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 28, Folder 24-26)
      - Notes, circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
      - Original Drawings by Reinhardt, circa 1960s (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Photographic Material, 1960-circa 1967 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        Includes photo of Ad Reinhardt and Lucy LIppard in 1960 with notation on verso "1st time we were introduced!"
      - Research Material (Box 29)
        - Announcements and Exhibition Catalogs, circa 1940s-circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Announcements and Exhibition Catalogs, 1940s-1950s (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - Announcements and Exhibition Catalogs, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 9)
          Oversized material housed in OV 66
        - Announcements and Exhibition Catalogs, 1974-1982 (Box 29, Folder 10)
        - Printed Material About Reinhardt, circa 1940s-circa 1970s (Box 29, Folder 11)
          Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 7
        - Printed Material About Reinhardt, 1944-1949 (Box 29, Folder 12)
        - Printed Material About Reinhardt, 1950-1959 (Box 29, Folder 13)
        - Printed Material About Reinhardt, 1960-1963 (Box 29, Folder 14)
          Oversized material housed in OV 64
        - Printed Material About Reinhardt, 1964-1965 (Box 29, Folder 15)
        - Printed Material About Reinhardt, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 16)
        - Printed Material About Reinhardt, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 17)
        - Printed Material About Reinhardt, 1975-1982 (Box 29, Folder 18)
        - Printed Material, General, circa 1930s-circa 1960s (Box 29, Folder 19-20)
        - Printed Material, General, 1937-1968 (Box 29, Folder 21)
        - Printed Material Illustrated by Reinhardt, circa 1930s-circa 1960s (Box 29, Folder 22)
          Includes copies of Reinhardt's "How to Look" series of "art reports from the Art-World" and "Out of the Horse's Mouth;" oversized material housed in OV 64
        - Printed Material Illustrated by Reinhardt, 1930s-1953 (Box 29, Folder 23)
        - Printed Material of Writings by Reinhardt, circa 1940s-circa 1970s (Box 29, Folder 24)
        - Printed Material of Writings by Reinhardt, 1940s-1950s (Box 29, Folder 25)
        - Printed Material of Writings by Reinhardt, 1960-1963 (Box 29, Folder 26)
        - Printed Material of Writings by Reinhardt, 1964-1966 (Box 29, Folder 27)
        - Reinhardt Correspondence, Photocopies, 1940s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 28)
        - Reinhardt Notes and Writings, Photocopies, circa 1940s-circa 1960s (Box 29, Folder 29-36)
        - Transcript of Interview of Reinhardt by Bruce Glaser, circa 1950s (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Books, Dadas on Art (1971) (Box 29)
      - Correspondence, circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 29, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 40)
      - Notes, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 41)
      - Research Material, circa 1960s (Box 29, Folder 42-43)
      - Research Material, circa 1960s (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
      - Research Material-Printed Material, circa 1930s-circa 1960s (Box 30, Folder 3-5)
    - Books, Eva Hesse (1976) (Box 30)
      - Correspondence and Notes, circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence and Notes, 1969-1973 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence and Notes, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence and Notes, 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Manuscript Corrections, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 10-11)
      - Manuscript, Corrected Galleys, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 12-15)
      - Manuscript Drafts, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 16-17)
      - Manuscript Front and End Matter, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 18-19)
      - Notes, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Notes from Hesse Correspondence and Diaries, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 21-22)
        Oversized material housed in OV 65
      - Research Material (Box 30)
        - Hesse Correspondence, Interviews and Writings, Photocopies, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 23)
        - Printed Material, Announcements and Exhibition Catalogs, circa 1964-1969 (Box 30, Folder 24)
        - Printed Material, Announcements and Exhibition Catalogs, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 25)
        - Printed Material, Clippings, circa 1950-1968 (Box 30, Folder 26)
        - Printed Material, Clippings, 1970-1974 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Books, From the Center: Feminist Essays on Women's Art (1976) (Box 30)
      - Correspondence, circa 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - Manuscript Drafts, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 29-31)
      - Notes, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 32-33)
    - Books, Get the Message?: A Decade Of Art For Social Change (1984) (Box 30)
      - Captions, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 34-35)
      - Corrected Galleys, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 36-38)
      - Correspondence and Outline, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 39-40)
      - Index, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Notes, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Part 1: The Dilemma, 1970s-1980s (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Part 2: Acting Out, 1970s-1980s (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Part 3: To the Third Power, 1970s-1980s (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Part 4: Hot Potatoes, 1970s-1980s (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Part 6: Collaborate! Demonstrate! Organize! Resist!, 1970s-1980s (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Photographic and Printed Material, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Proof, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 9-11)
      - Publication Permissions, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Publication Permissions, A-C, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Publication Permissions, D-K, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Publication Permissions, L-R, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Publication Permissions, S-Y, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Books, The Graphic Work of Philip Evergood (1966) (Box 31)
      - Correspondence and Notes, 1960s (Box 31, Folder 17-18)
      - Correspondence with Evergood, circa 1964 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence with Evergood, 1964-1966 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Manuscript and Page Proofs, 1960s (Box 31, Folder 21-22)
      - Photographs and Reproductions, circa 1960s (Box 31, Folder 23-24)
    - Books, I See/You Mean (1979), Correspondence Re. Sales, circa 1979-1981 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Books, Mixed Blessings: New Art in a Multicultural America (1990) (Box 31)
      - Correspondence and Contract, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence and Notes on Publication, 1980s-1990s (Box 31, Folder 27-29)
      - Gallery Copy, Bound, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 30)
        Existence and Location of Copies note
        partially scanned
      - Manuscript, Bibliography, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 31)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 1: Naming, Copy 1, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 32)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 2: Telling, Copy 1, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 33)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 3: Landing, Copy 1, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 4: Mixing, Copy 1, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 5: Turning Around, Copy 1, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 1: Naming, Copy 2, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 2: Telling, Copy 2, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 3: Landing, Copy 2, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 39)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 4: Mixing, Copy 2, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 40)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 5: Turning Around, Copy 2, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 1: Naming, Copy 3, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 2: Telling, Copy 3, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 3: Landing, Copy 3, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 4: Mixing, Copy 3, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 5: Turning Around, Copy 3, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 1: Naming, Copy 4, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Manuscript, Chapter 5: Turning Around, Copy 4, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Introduction, Mapping, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Notes, 1980s-1990 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Notes in Card File Box, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Books, Overlay: Contemporary Art and the Art of Prehistory (1983) (Box 32)
      - Bibliography, circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Book Proposal, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Bound Uncorrected Proof with Corrections by Lippard, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Captions, Introductions and Chapters 1 and 2, circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Captions, Chapters 3 and 4, circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Captions, Chapters 5 and 6 and Color Plates, circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Captions, Notes, circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Editing Process, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 20-23)
      - Footnotes, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Galley, Corrected, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 2-5)
      - Galley, Master Proof, Front and End Matter, circa 1982 (Box 33, Folder 6-7)
      - Index, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Manuscript, Corrected/Edited, Introduction and Chapters 1-2, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Manuscript, Corrected/Edited, Chapters 3-4, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Manuscript, Corrected/Edited, Chapter 5, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Manuscript, Corrected/Edited, Chapter 6 and Conclusion, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Manuscript, Corrected/Edited, Copy 2, Introduction and Chapters 1-2, 1980s; circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Manuscript, Corrected/Edited, Copy 2, Chapter 3, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Manuscript, Corrected/Edited, Copy 2,Chapter 4-5, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Manuscript, Corrected/Edited, Copy 2, Chapter 6, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Manuscript Drafts, Dedication and Introduction, 1980s (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Manuscript, Drafts and Notes, Chapter 1, 1980s (Box 33, Folder 18-19)
      - Manuscript, Drafts and Notes, Chapter 2, 1980s (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Manuscript, Drafts and Notes, Chapter 3, 1970s-1980s (Box 33, Folder 21-23)
      - Manuscript, Drafts and Notes, Chapter 4, 1970s-1980s (Box 33, Folder 24-25)
      - Manuscript, Drafts and Notes, Chapter 5, 1970s-1980s (Box 33, Folder 26-27)
      - Manuscript, Drafts and Notes, Chapter 6, 1970s-1980s (Box 33, Folder 28-30)
      - Manuscript, Unedited, Dedication and Introduction, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - Manuscript, Unedited, Chapters 1-2, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 32)
      - Manuscript, Unedited, Chapter 3, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 33)
      - Manuscript, Unedited, Chapter 4, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 34)
      - Manuscript, Unedited, Chapter 5, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 35)
      - Manuscript, Unedited, Chapter 6, circa 1980 (Box 33, Folder 36)
      - Notes, 1970s-1980s (Box 33, Folder 37)
      - Notes on Index Cards, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
      - Notes, "Possible Additions", 1980s (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Part 4: Mazes-Research Material, Correspondence and Notes, 1970s-1980s (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Part 6: Gardens-Research Material, Correspondence and Notes, 1970s-1980s (Box 34, Folder 5-6)
      - Publication Permissions, 1970s-1980s (Box 34, Folder 7-8)
      - Publicity, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Books, Pop Art (1966) (Box 34)
      - Correspondence and Notes, circa 1964-1967 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence and Notes, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence and Notes, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 12-13)
      - Correspondence and Notes, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Research Material, Printed Material and Notes, circa 1950s-circa 1960s (Box 34, Folder 15-16)
        Oversized material housed in Box 52 Folder 1
      - Research Material, Printed Material and Notes, 1956-1962 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Research Material, Printed Material and Notes, 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Research Material, Printed Material and Notes, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 19-20)
      - Research Material, Printed Material and Notes, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Research Material, Printed Material and Notes, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Research Material, Printed Material and Notes, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Books, Six Years: The Dematerialization of the Art Object (1973) (Box 34)
      - Captions, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence and Contract, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - Manuscript Draft, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - Manuscript "Uncut Version," Chapters 1966-1967, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Manuscript "Uncut Version," Chapter 1968, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 28-29)
      - Manuscript "Uncut Version," Chapter 1969, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 30-31)
      - Manuscript "Uncut Version," Chapter 1970, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 32-34)
      - Manuscript "Uncut Version," Chapter 1971, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 35-37)
      - Manuscript, Edited/Corrected, Chapters 1966-1967, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Manuscript, Edited/Corrected, Chapters 1968-1969, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - Manuscript, Edited/Corrected, Chapters 1969-1970, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - Manuscript, Edited/Corrected, Chapter 1970, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Manuscript, Edited/Corrected, Chapter 1971, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Notes, 1960s-1970s (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Notes on Index Cards, 1957-1966 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Notes on Index Cards, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Notes on Index Cards, 1967-1969 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Notes on Index Cards, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 7-9)
      - Notes on Index Cards, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 10-11)
      - Notes on Index Cards, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Notes on Index Cards, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 13-14)
      - Notes on Index Cards, Artists A-Z, circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Notes on Index Cards, Miscellaneous, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Notes on Index Cards, Numbered Cards, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Notes on Index Cards, Rejects, 1962-1968 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Photographs and Captions, 1970s; Includes 1 sound disc (vinyl), 45 rpm entitled "Terry Fox 'IsolationUnit', Dusseldorf Kuntsakademie 11-24-70" (Box 35, Folder 19-22)
      - Publication Permissions, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Research Material, circa 1968-circa 1972 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Supplement to Index, circa 1971 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Books, Surrealists on Art (1971) (Box 35)
      - Correspondence and Publication Permissions, circa 1966-1970 (Box 35, Folder 26-27)
      - Research Material, 1960s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 28-31)